Product + UX Designer

Stefanie Mendoza

<u>Portfolio</u> svm005@ucsd.edu

714.305.6250

Summary

A Product Designer who tackles complex problems by using her creativity, empathy, and curiosity to design impactful solutions. She has experience in conducting user research and visual design, taking ideas from concepts to prototypes that have received recognition and praise from mentors and stakeholders.

Skills

Tools: Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Indesign, After Effects, Figma, Sketch

Design: User Interface, Sketching, Wire-framing, User Research, User Testing, Prototyping, Paper Prototyping, A/B testing, Ethnographic Research

Development: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java (basic), Python (basic), Git, Heroku

Education

University of California, San Diego 2017-2021 B.S: Speculative Design Minor: Cognitive Science w/ Specialization in Design & Interaction

UC, San Diego Extension Front End Development Certification 2019-2020

Experience

UC San Diego Design Lab - Diabetes Design Initiative Intern Jun 2020 - Ongoing

Currently a project manager, conducting user research and design to reimagine diabetes education with DDI. We have Implemented a visualization data tool for people with diabetes around the world.

UC San Diego Design Lab - Dexcom Intern Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

In collaboration with industry partner, Dexcom and the Design Lab, I worked closely with my team of design students, Dexcom mentors, and DDI mentors to ideate and design for a unique 8 week Dexcom design challenge.